动作快点 伙计们 你们必须找到那个叛逃者
Hustle up, guys.
You've got to get that defector
然后带他离开 时间紧迫
and get the hell out of there. No delays.
嘿，鼠仔，你准备好了吗
你是不是从18岁起就期待这天到来了
Hey, Mouse, are you ready
with that 18-year-old aim?
是啊 长官
I'm on it, sir.
走 我们走
Move. Let's go.
好吧，来吧。
这家伙是在哪里？
All right, come on.
Where is this guy at?
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Come on, come on, come on.
好了 鼠仔 分散他们的主意力
All right, Mouse. Give us that diversion.
让我们继续前进。
Let's move.
弗林特，留在原地。
Flint, stay put.
我有没有说过你打架姿势很难看？
Anyone ever tell you you fight ugly?
他们倒下前你没说过
Not from their backs, they don't.
真该早点告诉你
It's just...
弗林特，我们走。弗林特？
Flint, let's go. Flint?
你在搞什么鬼
What the hell are you doing?
送他们份小礼物 长官。
Just marking our territory, sir.
盖恩士官，
如果你看到弗林特，给我毙了他。
Private Gaines,
if you see Flint, shoot him.
乐意效劳。
With pleasure.
客人已经接到 准备撤退
Defector in hand.
En route to pickup. Come on.
我没有看到他，你呢？
I don't see him, do you?
菲林 小心你身后的尾巴
Flint, get your ass
back to the team.
我们都在前进。
We are on the move.
你不会相信这事的 路霸
Uh, you ain't gonna
believe this, Roadblock.
靠...
Mother...
呀！
Yeah!
什么？
What?
不，不，不，不。不，不，不。
不公平的优势。
No, no, no, no. No, no, no.
Unfair advantage.
我更好。
I'm better.
他有光滑的脸颊。
他有没有面部毛发。
He's got smooth cheeks.
He's got no facial hair.
- 我要去拉针。
- 少一些摩擦在水下。
- I'm gonna pull the pin.
- There's less friction underwater.
这是一个犯规。这是一个犯规。
That's a foul. That's a foul.
特种兵标志。
A Joe flag.
一个特种兵的标志。
A G.I. Joe flag.
这是一个很好的接触，对不对？
That was a nice touch, right?
嗯。您可以调用它的。
Yeah. You can call it that.
你会怎么称呼呢？
And what would you call it?
- 不体面的。
- 是的，这一点。
- Undignified.
- Yeah, that, too.
你知道胜利，
我们应该成为绅士。
You know in victory,
we should be gentlemen.
哦！
Oh!
嘿，JAYE！
- 呦！
-Hey, Jaye!
- Yo!
能持续多久
一般的人屏住呼吸？
How long can
the average man hold his breath?
九十秒。
Ninety seconds.
- 搭把手。
- 你猜对了，老大。
- Free hand.
- You got it, boss.
好的。容易，弗利珀。
All right. Easy, Flipper.
嗯。
Mmm.
返回。妈的，这是很好的。
Back. Damn, that's good.
有没有错
与胜利的把握。它的乐趣。
There's nothing wrong
with taking a victory lap. It's fun.
这是它是如何工作的。特种兵是一个拳头。
This is how it works. G.I. Joe's a fist.
我们，我们是指关节。
Us, we're the knuckles.
我们怎么打呢？
How do we strike?
在一起。
Together.
手指的流浪狗...
A finger strays...
- 被打破。
- It gets broken.
指关节，再？真的吗？
Knuckles, again? Really?
作为一个朋友，
你要得到一个新的讲话。
As a friend,
you've got to get a new speech.
而接下来的时间
你想淹死有人，
And the next time
you want to drown somebody,
只是邀请我。
just invite me.
自去年底
的纳米虫战争，
Since the end
of the nanomite wars,
公爵成为了特种部队战术行动指挥官。
Captain Duke Hauser now leads
Joe Tactical Operations.
公爵领导的部下有路霸
Under Duke's command are Roadblock,
Jaye夫人，
Lady Jaye,
燧石
Flint
蛇眼。
and Snake Eyes.
无情的恐怖分子
眼镜蛇指挥官，
The ruthless terrorist known
as Cobra Commander,
并且Destro
and Destro
已经被特种部队
have been captured by the G.I. Joes
关押在戒备森严的监狱里
and placed in
a maximum security prison.
但是眼镜蛇操作工，风暴阴影
But the Cobra operatives, Storm Shadow
Zartan，仍然在逃。
and Zartan, remain at large.
单元和世界
The unit and the world
保持高度警惕以下
眼镜蛇指挥官的最后誓言。
remain on high alert following
Cobra Commander's final vow.
报复。
Retaliation.
看到的耳朵。
The ear that sees.
一个古老的的Arashikage测试。
An ancient Arashikage test.
金克斯，表弟风暴阴影，
Jinx, cousin to Storm Shadow,
它的时间来证明你已经准备好
加入G.I.的特种兵。
it's time to prove that you are ready
to join the G.I. Joes.
保卫自己。
Defend yourself.
我准备好了，硕士学位的盲人。
I'm ready, Blind Master.
耳朵，打开。
Ears, open.
蛇的眼睛，你的任务。
Snake Eyes, your task.
测试她的能力。
Test her abilities.
拨动一根头发从金克斯的头部。
Pluck a single hair from Jinx's head.
嗯，好。
Ah, good.
每个人都应该是灵活的猫，
One should be as nimble as a cat,
猛如虎。
yet fierce as a tiger.
蛇眼获胜。
Snake Eyes wins.
金克斯，为了在战争中脱颖而出，
Jinx, in order to excel in war,
首先，你必须找到和平。
you must first find peace.
蛇眼
Snake Eyes,
你们已赢得了正义之刃。
you have earned the Blade of Justice.
黑色碳纤维制成。
Made of black carbon fibre.
残酷的。坚不可摧。
Cruel. Indestructible.
有传言称，遭受新敌人的攻击
There are rumours of a new attack
by our enemies.
你必须离开道场 揭露这些阴谋，并阻止他们。
You must leave the dojo to uncover
these plans and stop them.
但是就算现在就出发。
你可能已经晚了。
But move swiftly.
You may already be too late.
开战！
Contact front!
敌人火力很强 我需要你更多支援 需要更多支援
Heavy enemy fire! I need you to bring
them up the line. Bring them up the tine.
收到路霸，
但我做不到，伙计。
Check that, Block,
but I can't, man.
我正在往回撤
I'm taking rounds back here.
我需要你！
现在，我需要你！
I need you!
I need you now!
空中打击 呼叫空中打击
Air strike! Call in an air strike!
等等 怎么才能呼叫空中打击
Wait. How do you call in
an air strike?
- 噢 - 我怎么样才能
- Jesus!
- Can I bring...
我怎么才能启用降落伞补给包呢 怎么用呢
What about one of those, like,
care package thingies?
我正在流血 我需要你马上向我方移动
I'm bleeding out
and I need you to sprint.
你只能用补给包吗 我能给你什么
Can you use a care package thingy?
I can bring you one.
你是在说补给包吗
A care package thingy?
谁在向我射击 怎么回事
Who is shooting me? What is...
我中弹在流血了 而你......
I'm bleeding out right there and you're...
你在打转吗
Are you spinning?
我在 我在全方位掩护你。
You got to cover 360.
- 你打转。
- 咦？
- You're spinning.
- Huh?
你实战多勇猛 怎么会这么菜
How could you be so good at combat?
You stink at this.
我才没有呢 你别太较真了 我本来就比你强
I think you need to relax.
I believe I outrank you,
- 最后一次检查 - 在我的主场 就未必
-last time I checked.
- Not in my house, you don't.
报告 我受到攻击了
-- Oh! All right. Taking fire!
敌人的炮火！超时！敌人的炮火！
Enemy fire! Time out! Enemy fire!
- 敌人接触！
-- Enemy contact!
公爵叔叔，你有大耳朵。
Uncle Duke, you have big ears.
你有一个大脑袋。
过来！
You got a big head.
Come here!
还击！什么，现在呢？
Returning fire! What's up, now?
还击！
Returning fire!
你不能尖叫，你的方式
出来的这一个！
You can't scream your way
out of this one!
是啊，请求援助，
哥哥！
Yeah, requesting assistance,
brother Block!
牵制，公爵兄弟。
牵制。
Pinned down, brother Duke.
Pinned down.
噢 快看看 看看是谁来了 小狗咬人了
That's all right. I got my boy here.
Demon dog!
奶奶 救命 他放狗咬我们
Grandma, help us!
We need backup!
你可不是头一回把女孩子吓得尖叫了
Not the first time you sent a girl
running out of the room screaming.
这次是头一回让两个女孩同时尖叫。
Not the first time
I sent two girls screaming from a room.
老兄，完全不合适。
Dude, completely inappropriate.
- 我只是说。
- 完全。
- I'm just saying.
- Completely.
暴力继续在巴基斯坦全境
Violence continues across Pakistan
在首都伊斯兰堡
in the capital of Islamabad
总统被暗杀之后
...
following the assassination
of President...
国家未来
The future of the country
和控制其核武库
仍是个未知数
and control of its nuclear arsenal
appear to be up in the air
袭击所造成的权力真空暂时
as the vacuum created
by the killing remains.
巴基斯坦
总统其实可能是死了，
The Pakistani
President may in fact be dead,
但巴基斯坦仍然是盟友。
but Pakistan remains an ally.
和一个主权国家。
And a sovereign nation.
曾经是
Was.
而现在她已经四分五裂了
Right now, they're a riot with a zip code.
总统 我们争分夺秒
Sir, every minute
we spend debating this,
想获得的核弹头
there are live nuclear warheads
坐在一片混乱。
that sit amidst the chaos.
我们不能让我们的敌人
首先得到这些弹头。
We can't let our enemies
get those warheads first.
各位有什么建议
Recommendations?
进去。
Go in.
现在。
Now.
等待和观望。
Wait and see.
有胆识者才能青史留名
History rewards the bold.
我可不是那种坐视不管的人
I'm not going to be the man
who waited and saw.
马上给我联络特种部队
Get me the G.I. Joes.
行星一号飞行指挥官 很快降落
Star One Flight commander
separating for drop.
好吧，听好了！
All right, listen up!
核武器的位置就在这附近 等抢到之后
That nuke cannot have gone far.
Once we have it,
就在回程途中解除引信！
we will disarm it en route to the L.Z.!
我们已经锁定导弹的装配设施
We have its location narrowed down
某处在这
导弹装配大楼。
to somewhere in this
missile assembly building.
我们从屋顶潜入 再从那里散开
We'll go in on the roof,
and fan out from there.
弗林特，JAYE，如果需要任何支持，
你们在后方提供支援
Flint, Jaye, if any support is needed,
you'll reinforce
路霸 你带领地面部队
as Roadblock leads the ground team.
地狱，是啊。
Hell, yeah.
嘿，鼠仔。
Hey, Mouse.
我第一次下降
我突然出现一个圆活了我嘴里。
On my first drop
I popped a live round into my mouth.
保持你的牙齿格格作响。
给它一个镜头。
Keeps your teeth from chattering.
Give it a shot.
- 美味。
- 干得好。
- Delicious.
- Attaboy.
JAYE，什么是我们反对？
Jaye, what are we up against?
武装叛乱分子
与卡拉什尼科夫冲锋枪，
Insurgents are armed
with Kalashnikovs,
SVD狙击枪 和50式冲锋枪
SVD Dragunovs and Type 50s.
冷战时期的东西。
Cold War stuff.
但还是可以把你们打成马蜂窝
But don't relax, boys,
still put holes in you.
哇！你有什么？
Whoa! What have you got there?
P-DUB 381黑色暴风雨
刚刚开箱。
P-dub 381 black Tempest,
just out of the box. Rounds.
四分之一的速度，远程控制。
Quarter speed, remote controlled.
我们什么时候得到这些吗？
When did we get these?
我们没有。我们做到了。
We didn't. We did.
特等射手专配
Distinguished Marksmen.
- 让我看看。
- 请勿触摸。
- Let me see.
- Don't touch.
女孩用枪支。
Girls with guns.
接近目标 准备出发
Approaching target.
Ten-hut! Make ready!
走吧！走吧！走吧！
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
怎么少了蛇眼？
Anyone else missing Snake Eyes?
我和蛇眼受训了六年
I trained with Snake for six years.
如果他不在这里，必有他的道理
If he ain't here, he's got good reason.
彩虹天使 准备降落
Arch-Angel, go for drop.
兄弟，一如既往
Brother Block, as always,
你会介意带领我们
几句话，好吗，先生？
would you mind leading us
in a few words, please, sir?
有一句不朽的名言
In the immortal words of Jay-Z,
“无论神可以指导我的生活，
"Whatever deity may guide my life,
“亲爱的主啊，不要让我死了今晚。
"dear Lord, don't let me die tonight.
“但是，如果我，在我醒来之前，
"But if I shall, before I wake,
- “我接受我的命运。”
- "I accept my fate."
地狱，是吗？
Hell, yeah?
地狱，是啊！
Hell, yeah!
地狱，是啊。
Hell, yeah.
设备检查！
Equipment check!
- 检查！
- Check!
-  跑得要比兔子快！
- Drive it like you stole it!
作为你的好朋友，
你需要一个新的流行语。
As your good friend,
you need a new catchphrase.
- 呼啊！
呼啊！
- Hoo-ah!
Hoo-ah!
A队 B队 无线电确认
Alpha, Bravo, radio check.
收到。
Copy.
没遇到敌人不要停
Go in ghost till first contact.
- 第三队第六队在地面上 - 收到
- Three and six on the floor.
- Copy that.
第二队 马上投入战斗 加大火力
Team two, expect heavy contact.
Bring the rain!
行动
Move out!
三队上楼。
Team three headed upstairs.
东走廊，明确的。
East hallway, clear.
二层已经安全 往三层移动
Level 2 secure.
Moving to level 3.
- 我欠你一个人情，鼠仔。
- 清除！
- I owe you one, Mouse.
- Clear!
好吧！我看见核武器了
All right! I got eyes on the nuke!
再说一遍，我看见核武器了！
Say again, I got eyes on the nuke!
我正在受到攻击
But I'm taking heavy fire!
稳坐！我走了弯路！
Sit tight! I'm taking a detour!
不，火石！
坚持计划！
Negative, Flint!
Stick with the plan!
探戈下来！
Tangos down!
走，走，走！
Go, go, go!
弗林特，状态！
Flint, status!
安全！
Fire now!
固定武器！
Weapons secured!
- 武器在4楼可以运输了
Equipment
pack-up on level four!
收到！
Set!
快 准备运输车 我们走
Clutch, station
the transport vehicle! Move!
所有小组 立即准备撤离
All teams,
rally to transpo, immediately.
叛乱分子收盘，先生！
Insurgents closing in, sir!
团队两个确保。任何的损失。
Team two secure. No losses.
- 总部联系。
- 我这一点。
- Contact headquarters.
- I'm on that.
安装了！
Mount up! Let's exfil.
- 跑道安全。
- 让安装！
- Runway secure.
- Let's mount up!
引信已经拆除
Nuke's disabled.
准备长距离运输 晚上7点钟落地
Long-range transportation
and wheels down at 1900 hours.
正好赶回家看电视。
Home in time for Top Chef.
干得好 小伙子
Good job, Tiny Tim.
看来玩射击游戏 挺管用
All that Wii Combat Shooter
finally paying off, sir.
巴姆！
Bam!
- 你好吗，先生？
- 好。
- How you doing, sir?
- Good.
这是人员名单
All Joes present and accounted for.
怎么样
Sit rep?
准备就绪 可以运送了 长官
Rendered safe
and ready for transport, sir.
确保安全 喝点啤酒
Square this one away and go get a beer.
- 听起来不错。
- 嗯，嗯。
- Sounds good.
- Mmm-hmm.
核弹安全并已拆除引信
Sir, the nukes have been
recovered and disabled.
特种部队顺利完成任务
All Joe missions successful.
仅受轻伤的报告，先生。
Only minor injuries to report, sir.
运输人员正在准备降落区 计划2点撤离
Transport crews are prepping
the L.Z. for evac at 0200 hours.
干得好，上尉。
Great job, Captain.
我们修改
您的开采计划，回到这里。
We're modifying
your extraction plan back here.
稳坐。
Sit tight.
走吧，里维拉，我们走吧。
Let's go, Rivera, let's go.
我丑话说前头
Let me get this straight.
一整个周末，
One whole weekend,
你照顾我的小女孩。
you looking after my little girls.
是的，只要我可以把这个。
Yep, as long as I can bring this.
你看，我爱你的孩子。我做的。
Look, I love your kids. I do.
但是，他们住恐吓我。
你他们训练得很好。
But they live to terrorise me.
You trained them well.
如果你赢了吗？
And if you win?
你就得接受升职任命
You have to take your next promotion.
你打一枪 我打一枪
You pull a trigger,
I pull a trigger.
一个做面包的 不一定能做得出好菜
I don't know if I'm gonna trust
a pastry from a gumbo chef.
考虑一下风向
Think about the wind.
四节？左到右。
Four knots? Left to right.
我说，湿度约62％。
Humidity, I say, is about 62%.
你要养活我
气压呢？
You gonna feed me
the barometric pressure, too?
这是在上升。喜欢你的内裤。
That's on the rise. Like your panties.
你爱我的内裤。
You love my panties.
这是一个有趣的选择了一个笑话。
That's an interesting choice of a joke.
你可以说所有的事情...
Of all the things you could say...
- “你爱我的内裤”？
- 是你要去闭嘴？
-"You love my panties"?
- Are you gonna shut up?
- 那是什么意思？
- 你会闭嘴吗？
- What does that mean?
- You gonna shut up?
- 我在寻找你。
- 我试图做一些事情。
- I'm looking out for you.
- I'm trying to do something.
我只是不...
- 闭嘴，闭嘴。
-I just don't...
- Shut up, just shut up.
- 我只是说。
- 闭嘴。
- I'm just saying.
- Just shut up.
你的心率怎么样？
How's your heart rate?
这是不是要去计数。
That is not gonna count.
我现在能去，因为你再次谈到。
I get to go again because you talked.
你拉到一个触发器。
现在，我拉一个触发器。
You pulled a trigger.
Now I pull a trigger.
不，我们不这样做。
No, we're not doing that.
- 那是不是要去计数。
-- That is not gonna count.
骗子。
Cheater.
我买了我的小女孩
卡拉OK机
I bought my little girls
a karaoke machine
他们喜欢唱歌就可以了，
通宵达旦。
and they love singing on it,
all night long.
有没有睡前宵禁，
所以他们要去会整夜。
There's no bedtime curfew,
so they're going to be up all night.
确保你把你的耳塞。
Make sure you bring your earplugs.
轰！
Boom!
- 回来 三局两胜 - 没门。
- C'mon, best two out of three.
- No.
三局两胜。这没算。
Best two out of three. That didn't count.
你没告诉我
关于卡拉OK机。
You didn't tell me
about the karaoke machine.
Zandar。
Zandar.
总统先生。
Mr President.
难道你不应该阻止人们
用枪射杀我的爸爸？
Aren't you supposed to stop people
from shooting my dad?
秃子。
Baldy.
白痴。
Idiot.
够挖出来，李·哈维。
Enough out of you, Lee Harvey.
清理的巧克力渍
你离开你母亲的卧室。
Go clean up the chocolate stains
you left in your mother's bedroom.
小鹰喜欢刮伤。
Kitty likes to scratch.
接下来的时间，
Next time,
拿出他的肥屁股。
take out his fat ass.
这将是我的荣幸，先生。
It would be my pleasure, sir.
我给你带来了一些消息。
I brought you some news.
特种部队就要被清理出视线以外了
The G.I. Joes are about to be
out of the picture.
我所说的被清理 意思就是
And by "out of the picture," I mean
从地球上消失
alive on earth.
因为他们爬得实在太高了
Got a little too close to Mount Olympus.
咦？
Huh?
该把他们打下来了
Had to strike them down.
他们揭穿到你，Zartan。
They'll find you out, Zartan.
不，我不这么认为。
No. No, I don't think so.
纳米技术的厉害就在于
That's the beauty of nanomites.
在这里，一起来看看。
Here, take a look.
嗯？
Hmm?
完美无瑕的显微技术。
Flawless microtechnology.
你疯了。
You're insane.
课间休息过。他坐了下来。
Recess over. Sit him down.
你知道，他们说
这是一个吃力不讨好的工作。
You know, they say
this is a thankless job.
但我在昨天还和歌手出去玩了
But yesterday I hung out with Bono.
我的新特勤局
My new Secret Service,
他们想烧宪法。
they want to burn the Constitution.
从字面上看。
Literally.
我的实习生...
And my interns...
哦，是啊，我带回来的实习生。
Oh, yeah, I brought back the interns.
嗯，嗯。
Mmm-mmm.
你知道我最喜欢的一点？
我吹的东西了。
Do you know my favourite bit?
I get to blow stuff up.
哦，我敢打赌，喜欢上你的人。
Oh, I bet that endears you to the people.
嗯，这是的东西。
Well, that's the thing.
你的支持率
爬上9分。
Your approval ratings
climbed nine points.
看来美国人喜欢的是你的长相
Apparently, America wants
someone who looks like you,
但行为像我一样。
but acts like me.
我做事从不拖泥带水，宝贝。
I'm the quicker blower-upper, baby.
但有一点不满意
Only one drawback.
你那位亲爱的夫人
The little wifey-pooh?  Huh?
如果你碰我的家人...
If you touch my family...
我唬弄你。
I'm yanking your chain.
你都做到第二任了，
Two long terms of you,
我只是一个短短的几个月。
just a few short months of me.
所以我们不要浪费时间。
So let's not waste the time I got left.
告诉我监狱在哪儿
眼镜蛇指挥官和Destro关哪儿？
Where is the prison that holds
Cobra Commander and Destro?
这是我问你，
你有什么计划吗？
Is this where I ask you,
what do you have planned?
为什么没有人想成为总统？
Why does anyone want to be President?
每个人都想要统治世界。
Everybody wants to rule the world.
所有队员
我们准备撤离了
All squads,
gear up and clear the L.Z.
准备开启一号机库
Prepare for extraction.
要撤离了 不需要我们了
Extraction? What are we, teeth?
- 到达H.Q.？
- 不，我什么也没得到。
- Reach H.Q.?
- No, I got nothing.
- 联络上了吗。
- 好的 中士。
- Go up high.
- Roger, Sarge.
路霸。
Block.
我们的人都还在 没有一个人伤亡
All our men accounted for.
Not a single drop of blood.
- 干得漂亮。
- 是的，先生。
- Boots to asses.
- Yes, sir.
你没事吧...
你刮你的胳膊肘？
Except for that...
Did you scrape your elbow?
- 不，这是红色的汗水。
- 是啊。
- No, it's red sweat.
- Yup.
这更好的了
某人的脸。
That better have been
on somebody's face.
嘿，公爵。
Hey, Duke.
你看到了吗？
You see that?
后续部队
Security's early.
- 趴下！
- Get down!
- Take cover!
快找掩护！
Take cover!
拿上武器！走吧！
To your weapons! Let's go!
趴下 趴下
On the ground! On the ground!
鼠仔！
Mouse!
快跑 兄弟
Get 'em out of the L.Z.!
受伤了
Medic!
去！
Go!
弗林特！受伤了！
Flint's down! Flint's down!
- 我去救他！
- ！
- I'm going for him!
- Go!
十点钟方向
Ten o'clock!
趴下！
Get down!
部队接触！
立即请求空中支援！
Troops in contact!
Request immediate air support!
我再说一遍，直接空中支援！
I repeat, immediate air support!
你没事吧？来吧，我们必须要继续前进！
走，走，走！
You all right? Come on, we got to move!
Go, go, go!
帮帮我吧！
Help me!
怎么样 没事吧
You good? You hit?
路霸，我找到了火石。我们需要掩护！
Block, I got Flint. We got to get to cover!
来吧。
Come on.
来袭！来袭！走，走，走，走，走！
Incoming! Incoming! Go, go, go, go, go!
公爵，进来。
Duke, come in.
公爵！
Duke!
快点找掩护
Get to cover, now!
去！
Go!
- 撤退 快到集结点
- 快去！
- Pull back! Rally point!
- Let's go!
快到井去！
Get to the well! Go!
从那边过来了
Clear 'em out of there.
隐蔽
Fall back! Fall back!
这儿也没问题
We're clear.
走吧！
Let's go!
我们已经遇到了敌人
We have met the enemy
他就是我们自己。
and he is us.
今天世界上最精锐的著名的特种部队
Today, the world's elite fighting force,
the G. I. Joes,
背叛了自己的职责
abandoned their duty
他们已经辜负了
and broke the sacred bond
that exists between
美国人民
the American people
对他们保卫安全的嘱托
and those entrusted with their security.
准备好了 上
Ready and step.
准备
Ready and
上！
step!
他们所走的第一步就是暗杀了巴基斯坦总统
The first domino fell with
the murder of the Pakistani president.
刺客
The assassin,
是一个特种兵，
a Joe,
他的代号
call sign
蛇眼。
Snake Eyes.
但他并没有单独行动。
But he didn't act alone.
特种部队就是准备利用混乱的局面
The Joes intended to use this situation
控制巴基斯坦的核武库。
to seize Pakistan's nuclear arsenal.
现在这个事件
Now this incident
再次向我们敲响警钟 谨防核武器带来的灾难
serves as a sobering reminder
of the scourge of nuclear weapons.
为了达成目标
And to that end,
我呼吁我的同胞世界各国领导人
I call upon my fellow world leaders
立即召开会议，讨论
to convene immediately to discuss
核裁军。
nuclear disarmament.
三个。
On three.
- 一个。
- One.
二。
Two .
三！
Three!
G. I.特种兵
The G. I. Joes
完全超出了他们的授权任务范围
clearly went beyond
the boundaries of their mission.
在我的命令下
On my orders
一个隐蔽的特种部队
代码名为眼镜蛇
a covert Special Forces unit
code named Cobra
他们执行命令 已经彻底消灭了他们的
terminated with extreme prejudice
Joe Command,
人员和设施
facilities, personnel.
特种部队不存在了。
The G.I. Joes are no more.
我们应该离开。
We should leave.
这里什么都没了
There's nothing here.
There's nothing left here?
- 这不是他的意思！
- 这些都是我们的兄弟！
- That's not what he meant!
- These are our brothers!
这不是他的意思！
That's not what he meant!
昨晚来的敌人一定会再回来
Whoever did this is going to come back.
我们得赶紧走
We need to move.
你现在是我们的领袖。
You are our leader now.
我们前往正东，直到我们清楚。
We head due east until we're clear.
我们要找到这些人
谁这样干掉公爵
We're gonna find the man
who did this to Duke
我们的兄弟。
and our brothers.
我们会杀了他。
And we're gonna kill him.
蛇眼。
Snake Eyes.
这是你最后的终点
Last place I thought I'd see you.
监狱长詹姆斯。幸会
Warden James. It's a pleasure.
我是你的忠实粉丝 我喜欢你的黑色
I'm a very big fan. I love the black.
那是相当的时尚
It's very Johnny Cash.
你来吧。欢迎来到地下监狱
Come. Welcome to Einsargen.
让我告诉你一点点
约的地方。
Let me tell you a little bit
about the place.
听我说。
我听起来像一个真正的房地产经纪人。
Listen to me.
I sound like a real-estate agent.
我不是在这里向你推销什么。
I'm not here to sell you anything.
也许除了绝望。
Except maybe hopelessness.
这次旅行怎么样？
How was your trip?
你现在是不是觉得有点头重脚轻
The sensation that you're feeling,
your upside-down tummy?
这是由于我们进入
一个前东德矿井。
It's due to our descent into
a former East German mine shaft.
这是他们曾经挖最深的。
It was the deepest they ever dug.
如此之深，事实上，
你刚刚跨过德国
So deep in fact that
you just crossed out of Germany
进入国际领土。
into international territory.
这让我
Which allows me
某些司法管辖区的自由。
certain jurisdictional freedoms.
咦？
Huh?
有一个词，
One word,
真棒。这间客房是真棒！
awesome. This room is awesome!
这里的温度超过210度
Temperatures here exceed 210 degrees
但我们有了人工降温的装置 降到了68度
when not artificially cooled to a crisp 68.
差不多都可以穿得上长袖衬衫
Almost calls for a Snuggie.
接下来的更精彩
Wait till you see this next one.
明白我的意思吗？我都被震撼到了
See what I mean? This just slays me.
它是如此有趣。
这就是科技的最前沿
It's so interesting.
This is where science has come.
你知道吗，在浅度睡眠状态
Did you know that during REM sleep,
人体
the human body
产生的神经化学物质
produces a neural chemical
瘫痪身体的每一块肌肉
which paralyses
every muscle in the body
但心脏和眼睛除外
这可以防止我们
but the heart and the eyes?
This prevents us
在睡梦中身体乱动
from acting out our dreams.
我们给这两位都已经注射了
We have injected both of these men
这种合成化学物质
with a synthetic version.
他们是完全清醒的。
他们是有意识的，
They're perfectly awake.
They're conscious,
他们知道的一切
他们周围的一切。
they're aware of everything
that's going on around them.
这只是他们
自己被困在里面。
It's just that they're
trapped inside themselves.
好吧，我相信你知道
您的新邻居，毁灭，
Well, I believe you know
your new neighbours, Destro,
眼镜蛇指挥官。
Cobra Commander.
哦，你们三个一起凑成了我的梦之队
Oh, the three of you are like
my fantasy football team.
先生们。
Gentlemen.
现在你的眼睛和心灵
Now as your eyes and mind
旅行，你不能，
我要你烦恼。
travel to where you cannot,
I want you to agonise.
让你的忧伤
I want you to pine.
让你的痛苦 那种程度一般人有过一次就不想再有
I want you to ache for what once was
and will never be again.
我会让你再也不想着逃跑了
I want you to doubt
that there was ever a word for escape.
欢迎来到地狱。
Welcome to hell.
你根本就不知道
You have no idea.
蛇眼说话了。
Snake Eyes speaks.
我想象不出你说话时的声音
It never occurred to me
what you might sound like.
不过我很想知道你到底长什么样
But I've always thought about
what you might look like.
摘下面具吧
We'll have that mask.
风暴阴影。
Storm Shadow.
所以，你杀了巴基斯坦总统。
So you killed the Pakistani president.
你虽然不是我的首选对象
Well, you're not exactly
my first-round draft pick,
但我永远是你的粉丝
but I've always been a fan.
按规定 我们该发出求救信号吗
Protocol says we make
a distress call, right?
不 部队都没了 还要什么规定
No.
Protocol died with the unit.
什么？
What?
那怎么让人知道我们还活着
How's anybody gonna know we're alive?
没必要 我们死了
They're not, 'cause we're not.
政府这么想
To our government,
我们的家庭，
但尤其是我们的敌人，
to our families,
but especially to our enemy,
也都以为我们早上6点已经在河谷沙漠阵亡了
we were KIA at 0600 hours
in the Indus Valley Desert.
但是，我们必须至少尝试。
我的意思是，有可能是...
But we have to at least try.
I mean, there might be...
不 现在做什么都无法证明清白
No. Anything we do now
is a rumour of a rumour.
任何和所有的痕迹
Any and all traces
都被抹去了
of our existence is terminated.
我们现在唯一能信任的只有蛇眼
The only one I trust out there
is Snake Eyes.
当我们腹背受敌，
When we got hit,
我们怎么腹背受敌
how we got hit,
都是预先设计好的
we were set up right from the start.
多高的军衔才能
How many stars would
someone need on their shoulder
调用这样的攻击？四星？五星？
to call an attack like that? Four? Five?
不，不是星级。他的西装上的按钮。
No, not stars. Buttons on his suit.
国家安全顾问。
国防部长。
National Security Advisor.
Secretary of Defence.
号只有一个人
谁可以授权这样的一击。
No. There's only one man
who could authorise a strike like that.
我投他的票。
And I voted for him.
眼镜蛇指挥官主要生命指标正常
All Vitals
on Cobra Commander are steady.
风暴阴影
注射神经合成素。
Storm Shadow
nerve prohibitors injected.
62度 浮动范围是4%
Sixty-two degrees on a change of 4%.
有空袭  趴下
Aerial threat! Down!
我们要回家了。
We're going home.
警报 警报
Full arrest! Full arrest!
心跳停止了 这不是演习
No drill! Bring the restraints!
把容器的盖子掀开
Remove the containment lid!
血清在哪里？赶快行动吧！
Where's the serum? Quickly!
现在肾上腺素。现在！肾上腺素！
Adrenaline now. Now! Adrenaline!
走吧！快，快！
Let's go! Quickly, quickly!
快 快
Move! Move!
血清在哪里？
Where's the serum?
快上 快
Let's go!
他摆脱了 快
Peel back! Move!
你是什么意思，
他的心脏停止跳动吗？
What do you mean,
his heart stopped beating?
这里没有人死，除非是我说的！
No one here dies unless I say so!
哦，我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
开枪
Fire!
开枪 开枪
Fire! Fire!
- 干掉他！
- Take him down!
干掉他！
Take him down!
北边安全！
Clear on the north!
安全！
Clear!
欢迎来到地狱。
Welcome to hell.
停！
Stop!
不管什么从里头出来 都通通干掉
You shoot anything
that walks through that door!
格杀勿论
Anything!
风暴阴影。
Storm Shadow.
果然不负我期望
Never a doubt.
眼镜蛇指挥官。
Cobra Commander.
毁灭。
Destro.
你已经被开除了
You're out of the band.
来吧。
Come on.
我看你已经安排接应了。
I see you've arranged transportation.
我早上9点前引发的爆炸量
Making more things go boom
by 9:00 a.m.
比大多数人做了一整天还多。
than most people do all day.
萤火虫。很高兴见到你，老朋友。
Firefly. Good to see you, old friend.
长官
Sir.
有些人只是不想让我进去。
Some people
just didn't want to let me in.
现在，我打掉了8个监狱。
Now, I busted out of eight prisons.
但我只闯进一个。
But I only broke into one.
所有通信已经截止。
没有人会知道你竟然不翼而飞。
All communications have been cutoff.
No one will know you're even missing.
带他到山上去治疗
Take him
to the mountains to heal.
我准备发动的战争里还用得上他
I'll need him
for the war I'm about to start.
- 我想帮助你。
- I want to help you.
我们已经看到了风暴的伤害。
我们知道他在哪里的领导。
We've seen Storm's injuries.
We know where he's headed.
你需要我。
And you need me.
好。
Good.
长官，发射控制是差不多了。
进度一直被总监拖延
Sir, launch controls are nearly up.
The director was running behind.
他已经用不着拖延了 另外找人接管就是了
Well, he ain't running behind no more.
Or anywhere else, for that matter.
装甲原型
完全按您要求制作
Armour prototype
is complete to your specs.
我把测控器调到60了
I got it up to 60 on the dyno today.
你会喜欢这个 新头衔，
You'll like this. Working title,
高速哨兵。简称西斯。
High Speed Sentry. HISS.
这是很好的你，先生。
It's good to have you back, sir.
她是不是一个美女？
Ain't she a beauty?
很快世界
将畏缩在宙斯面前。
Soon the world
will cower in the face of Zeus.
您能回来真好 指挥官。
All we've been missing
is our Commander.
很酷的面具。
Cool mask.
有些人很悠闲呐
Someone took his time.
要溜出那座白色大房子可不容易
Not easy to sneak out of that big, white,
11间卧室，35间半厕所...
11-bedroom, 35-and-a-half bath...
只是不要忘了
Just don't forget who put you there.
你是从哪儿爬出来的
Or the rock you crawled out from.
萤火虫。很高兴我们还是这样疯狂
Firefly. It's good to know
we're not running low on crazy.
所有10个手指吗？
Still all 10 fingers?
我们的前总统是如何呢？
How is our former President?
哦，他的利用价值可高了
Oh, he is worth his weight in platinum.
有一种酷刑叫水刑
You know, they call it a waterboard,
但我从来不觉得无聊。
but I never get bored.
48小时之后 宙斯将会发射
In 48 hours,
Zeus will launch.
但是有个小问题
Just one wrinkle.
三名特种队员侥幸逃过一劫
Three Joes somehow survived
our little house cleaning.
一架无人机在河谷沙漠侦测到声波信号
A drone picked up voiceprints
in the Indus Valley.
我能相信你什么？
Can I trust you with nothing?
他们会滑倒。
They'll slip up.
当他们这样做，
And when they do,
我会追捕他们到地面。
I'll hunt 'em to ground.
呼啊。
Hoo-ah.
不，不，这很酷。
No, no, it's cool.
我得到了它。
I got it.
你迷路了吧，小个子？
You lost, little man?
不，我不会迷路。
No, I ain't lost.
我觉得你走错路了吧。
I think you got the wrong street.
你为什么不往麦莉赛勒斯走
So why don't you take Miley Cyrus
瑞安西克赖斯
and Ryan Seacrest
给我绕别的路
and head back that way?
我就要走这条道
I'm going that way.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
嗯。
Yeah.
来吧，马文。
Go ahead, Marvin.
嘿，不叫我这个名字。
Man, don't call me that name.
- 怎么了？小马文！
-- What's up? Little Marvin!
- 马文？
- 现在是大马文了。
- Marvin?
- Big Marvin now.
对不起 让你们担心了一下
Had you worried for a minute, man.
别乱动 朋友 小心受伤
Watch your hand back there, boy.
You don't want them to get you.
看着你长大了。
Look at you. You got grown.
你的父母怎么养大你的
How your parents
make a kid this big, man?
- 他的父母养他很容易的。
- 真的吗？
- His parents are like 5'2" apiece.
- Really?
你服用P90X 很严重的，对吧？
You're taking
that P90X serious, huh?
每周两次。
Twice a week.
我明白。看在你的脖子的大小。
I see. Look at the size of your neck.
让我给你介绍一下。这是弗林特。
Let me introduce you. This is Flint.
怎么了？
What up?
Jaye夫人。
Lady Jaye.
Jaye夫人。嘿。
Lady Jaye. Hey.
- 欢迎回来。
- 谢谢你。
- Welcome back.
- Thank you.
这是发生了什么
当你有麻烦时，你回家。
It's what happens
when you're in trouble, you come home.
家永远会帮你。
Home is where the help is.
阿门。
Amen.
我们都支持你
Well, we got you.
这里可以当指挥中心
Set up at the rec centre.
低调。
没有人会打扰你。
Lay low over there.
Nobody gonna bother you.
至于出行方面
As far as wheels go,
我会让你开我的卡车。
I'm gonna let you roll my truck.
谢谢。
Thank you.
我这车贷还没交完呢
I got payments on that truck, man.
我不明白，像我以前。没事吧？
I don't get it like I used to. All right?
谢谢，哥们儿。
Thank you, Stoop.
我欠你一个人情，兄弟。
I owe you one, brother.
其实，你欠我两个。
Actually, you owe me two.
- 另一个不能算。
- That other one don't count.
欢迎回家，马文。
Welcome home, Marvin.
留神脚下。
Watch your step.
这儿荒废多年 可以作为藏身之地使用
No one's been here for years.
This is gonna have to be our pit for now.
哇。这个地方不错。
Wow. It's an actual pit.
我以前最喜欢来这儿了
It's my old stomping ground.
你确定
我们可以相信这个托普家伙？
Are you sure
we can trust this Stoop guy?
- 斯托普不是天使。
- Stoop's no angel.
但他是一家人，我们可以信任他。
But he is family and we can trust him.
我们可以追溯到吗？
Can we be traced?
我们可以掩盖我们的IP地址。
We can mask our IP addresses.
我会每六小时改一次编码信号
I'll cyber-blast an encoded beacon
every six hours.
如果还有弟兄活着
If any Joes did survive,
我们需要让他们知道
我们在哪里。
we need to let them know
where we're at.
好的。好吧，让我们去上班。
All right. Well, let's get to work.
弗林特，你来清点留下的所有装备
Flint, inventory every piece
of equipment we got left.
JAYE，建立数据库调查总统
Jaye, start that database
on our President.
我们会发现这位最高统帅到底是怎么了
We'll find out what's going on
with our Commander-in-Chief.
他可不像我们认识的那个人了 找出背后原因
He's not acting like the man we know.
We find out why,
我们就可以恢复军人身份了
we can start being soldiers again.
中尉Jaye夫人，
请求紧急援助。
Lieutenant Lady Jaye,
requesting immediate aid.
如果任何特种兵幸存...
If any Joes have survived...
这是特种部队专属频道吧
This channel's restricted to Joes,
isn't it?
方位是 4-5-4-3 西部波托马克。
...magnetic west of the Potomac.
他们还活着。
They're alive.
这是Jaye夫人中尉
请求紧急援助。
This is Lieutenant Lady Jaye
requesting immediate aid.
中尉Jaye夫人，
这是金克斯和蛇眼。
Lieutenant Lady Jaye,
this is Jinx and Snake Eyes.
我们都在追捕风暴阴影。
We are in pursuit of Storm Shadow.
即使蛇眼和金克斯
抓到风暴，
Even if Snake Eyes and Jinx
grab Storm,
可他们也在地球的另一边
they're still halfway around the world.
我们得靠自己了
We're on our own.
足够为一个战斗。
Enough for a battle.
打大仗不够
Not a war.
我们的敌人很强大
We're fighting uphill here.
我第一次来这儿的时候才14岁 人家以为我死了
I came here when I was 14
with a life expectancy of 13.
我不停地改变藏身的地点 直到来这儿
I was bounced around
from home to home, until this
成了我的家。
became my home.
人们在外面排队 等着跟我打架
Guys were lined up
outside that door to fight me.
这么多，他们直喊我瘦屁股
从中取乐
They whooped my skinny ass so much
I started to enjoy it.
直到一个冬天，
Till one winter,
我增长了8英寸，并获得了60磅。
I grew 8 inches and gained 60 pounds.
把一个家伙打得半身不遂爬不动为止
I punched a guy so hard
he couldn't move his arm to tap out.
特种部队来这儿招兵的时候
Then when the Joes
came recruiting to the hood,
我打倒了他们一半的人
I'd already beaten down half of it.
我成了特种部队的一员 上了前线
I became a Joe to serve. In the field.
如果对手真的很强大 那就让他们来吧
So if we're fighting uphill,
we take the hill.
嗨 我有东西要给你们看
Hey, I got something
you'll want to see.
我在调查总统时有了新发现
During my check of the President,
look what I found.
这是8月9日的总统。
This is the President on August 9th.
过多地仰赖境外能源供给
...an addiction
to offshore energy,
我们被迫卷入
where we're forced to be
kind of embroiled
在外国的事务。
in the affairs of foreign nations.
这是10天后。
And this is 10 days later.
否则，我的意思是，我们有点...
I mean, otherwise, we're sort of...
这些都是会话惯用语
These are conversational fillers.
Little phrases
是人随口说出的
we spit out to give our brain
a chance to catch up
以填补思考间隙的词语。喜欢...
with our mouth. Like...
- 喜欢。
- 是的。
- Like.
- Yes.
我们的总统呢？
And our President?
8月9日和8月19日之间，
Between August 9th and August 19th,
他停止使用
“你知道”和“有点”
he stopped using
"you know" and "kind of"
并开始使用“我的意思是”和“之类的。”
and started using "I mean" and "sort of."
但是，这还不是全部。
“晚餐”成为“吃饭。”
But that's not all.
"Supper" became "dinner."
“苏打水”成为“汽水”。
"Soda" became "pop."
一个总统，说话两种风格。
One President, two fingerprints.
但它是一个几句话，对不对？
我的意思是，能有多大......
But it's a few words, right?
I mean, how much can...
再往下看
Check this out.
两个新闻发布会，
7月31日，9月1日。
Two press conferences,
July 31st, September 1st.
注意他的手指
See his fingers clasped?
左手拇指之上
与右手拇指在上面。
Left thumb on top
versus right thumb on top.
同一个人绝不可能会这样
The same person
never does this differently,
感到不对劲。
it feels wrong.
如果总统
What if the President
不是他本人呢
isn't the President?
如果最高统帅都可以冒名顶替
Look, if the Commander-in-Chief
is an imposter
而且他下令攻击，
and he's the one that ordered the attack,
那我们就谁也不可能信任了 对不对
we have to assume
that there's no one we can trust.
有一个人。
There is one man.
他的理由，我们称自己为特种兵。
He's the reason we call ourselves Joes.
喂？
Hello?
我会买两包薄荷味饼干和一盒巧克力
I'll take two cases of Thin Mints
and a box of Chuckle Lucks.
放下你的武器。
Lower your weapons.
科尔顿，恕我冒昧...
General Colton, if I may...
闭上你的嘴，布伦达。
Shut your mouth, Brenda.
我的名字不是布伦达。
My name's not Brenda.
你怎么进来？
How'd you get in?
先生，道歉。
Sir, apologies.
- 我是马文中士...
- 我知道你是谁。
- Sergeant Marvin...
- I know who you are.
那您该知道我为什么来
Then you know why I'm here.
我一直在想你们说的
It's not like
I don't hear what you're saying.
总统 竟是个冒牌货
But an imposter President?
被将军一说
这听起来很疯狂？
How come when the General says it,
it sounds crazy?
那真的总统怎么样了？
What'd they do with the real President?
我们担心他已经死了。
We fear he's dead.
我不这么想 有用的人质你是不会杀的
I don't think so.
You're not going to kill your best asset.
“康拉德公爵豪瑟”。
"Conrad Hauser. Duke."
你的队长。
Your captain.
告诉我一件事，你对他的了解。
Tell me one thing you know about him.
伟大的战士。
Great soldier.
更好的朋友。
Better friend.
他救了我的命，先生。
And he saved my life, sir.
好。
Good.
你提出的是叛国罪。
What you're proposing is treason.
我会需要比拇指重叠
I'm gonna need something
a little more to go on
更多的证据。
than overlapping thumbs.
在你退休之前，
你担任一个安全事务委员会
Before you retired,
you served on a security commission
总统的参谋长。
with the President's Chief of Staff.
将军科尔顿，你能不能让我们更接近？
General Colton, can you get us close?
不行。
Negative.
在这个小镇，我一有小动作就会被列入黑名单。
I can't scratch my ass in this town
without getting on the watch list.
布伦达，递给我那支笔。
Brenda, hand me that pen.
这下我又变成秘书了
Girl Scout to secretary.
接着 我不叫布兰达
Amazing. Name's not Brenda.
这只是一支笔。
It's just a pen.
大道K，乔治敦。晚上九时
Avenue K, Georgetown. 9:00 p.m.
参谋长在那儿打扑克牌
There's a poker game
with the Chief of Staff there.
他不是一个好的扑克选手。
He's not a good poker player.
每次都破绽百出
He's got 1,000 tells.
我们只需要一个。
We only need one.
嘿，亲爱的。
Hey, hon.
刚打完牌出来 输了点 但长了经验
Just got out of poker. Poorer but wiser.
其实这是一个很好的一天。
It was a good day, actually.
佩雷斯
总统他吃错药了。
The Prez was taking
his crazy pills again.
宝贝，我要去给你回电话。
Baby, I'm gonna have to call you back.
嗯。
Yeah.
爱你。
Love you.
对不起。
Excuse me.
哦，嗨。
Oh, hi.
嗨。
Hi.
要不要我帮个忙
You need a hand with your bags?
当然。
Sure.
没问题。你去那里。
No problem. There you go.
谢谢。
Thank you.
你真有骑士风度
Who said chivalry is dead, right?
骑士风度
Chivalry.
那是不是有追兵要找我的麻烦呢
Talk like that,
I'm gonna get myself in trouble.
我们向何处去？
Where we heading?
那边 拐弯
Just right around the corner.
刺痛的感觉是异戊巴比妥。
That tingly feeling is amobarbital.
会造成失忆的镇静剂
It's a sedative that causes
anterograde amnesia.
五分钟后，你会是睡着了。
In five minutes, you're gonna be asleep.
再过5分钟，你会醒来
忘记我曾经存在过。
In another five, you're gonna wake up
with no idea I ever existed.
有没有发现总统怪怪的
Notice anything strange
about your boss?
也许吧。为什么呢？
Maybe. Why?
你要帮我们打一个电话。让我们靠近他。
'Cause you're gonna make
a phone call for us. Get us close to him.
不过不用担心。
你会忘记一切，
But don't worry.
You're gonna forget everything,
你的意识也会恢复
so your conscience will be clear.
你为什么这样做？
Why are you doing this?
就算我告诉你你也不信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
拨打电话。
Make the call.
哦！
Oh!
感谢上帝。
Thank God.
总统先生最近意气风发
El Presidente is on a roll.
支持率在增长
His numbers are up.
我不只是在谈论他的年龄。
And I'm not just talking about his age.
我现在可不想讨论他的八卦
Now, I'm not gonna call
our Commander-in-Chief old.
毕竟他已经是高龄人士了
Actually, he called me the other day
for some advice.
- 晚上好。
- Good evening.
他希望能将美国的核武器装备
He wanted to hook up
the nation's nuclear arsenal
用来吓小鸟
to the Clapper.
对不起，小姐，你......
I'm sorry, ma'am, you're...
迟到了，我知道。
Late, I know.
我用了一个军队的人才打扮成这样
Imagine the army it takes
to make me look like this.
说实话 我很愿意加入那个军队
Forgive me.
That's an army I'd like to enlist in.
再查一下
Speaking of lists,
能否解释下您怎么没在名单上
would you like to explain
why you're not on ours?
她在这儿 办公厅主任的人
Here she is. Chief of Staff.
祝您今晚愉快，德沃特小姐。
Enjoy your evening, Miss Vandervoort.
我进来
I'm in.
收到。请待命。
Roger that. Standing by.
JAYE？
Jaye?
你要尽量低调 保证安全
You keep your head down. Be safe.
卡维尔先生 采纳了我的一项主张
Mr Carville was
nice enough to mention
核武器的裁减
one of my passions.
Nuclear disarmament.
就在几天后
In just days,
八个有核国家的最高元首
the leaders of the world's
eight nuclear nations
将聚集在历史悠久的萨姆特堡
will gather at historic Fort Sumter
举行核峰会。
for a nuclear summit.
在核八国峰会之前
But before the Atomic Eight
break bread,
轮到我们了。
it's our turn.
谢谢你，詹姆斯。谢谢。
Thank you, James. Thank you so much.
总统先生。
艾米德沃特，福克斯新闻。
Mr President.
Amy Vandervoort, Fox News.
哦，福克斯，当然。
Oh, Fox, of course.
这就是为什么你看起来那么
“客观和平衡。”
That's why you look so
"fair and balanced."
很可爱。
但实际上，我是希望有一个...
Very cute.
But I was actually hoping to have a...
跳舞？
Dance?
- 我想请您谈谈。
- 嗯。
- I was going to say, quote.
- Ah.
好吧 那我就说两句
Okay, here's a quote.
世界将因即将召开的核峰会而改变
The world will change
after my nuclear summit.
怎么样，我们跳舞吗？
How about we dance?
我真的...不太会跳舞。
I really, I don't dance.
抱歉。
Sorry.
谢谢你，总统先生。
你给我我需要什么。
Thank you, Mr President.
You gave me what I need.
我得回去赶稿子了
But I really have to make my deadline.
- 这真是我的荣幸。
- 谢谢你。
- It's been a pleasure.
- Thank you.
你怎么样？
How are you?
好，总统阁下。
Good, sir.
我从他的外套得到了一缕头发
我希望这是够用的。
I got a strand of hair
from his jacket. I hope it's enough.
快快。
Come on.
收到了。
Copy that.
正准备身份确认
Standing by for I.D.
所有单位，橙色警报。
警戒。
All units, setting condition orange.
Stand by.
还没有人敢对我说不呢
I don't take no for an answer.
快完成了
Almost there.
来吧，来吧，来吧，来吧。
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Zartan？
Zartan?
JAYE，快离开那里。
Jaye, get out of there now.
哦，我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
查到她的身份了 是特种部队的
We have an unauthorised I.D.
She's a Joe.
有特种部队潜入
We have a Joe on the premises.
JAYE。
Jaye.
JAYE，快走。
Jaye, now.
我出来。
I'm out.
“B计划”，布拉沃汇合。
Plan B, rendezvous Bravo.
改了，在查理汇合。
Negative.
Proceed to rendezvous Charlie.
查理。
Charlie.
什么意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
对不起，JAYE。
Sorry, Jaye.
我在这里能搞定。
I got it from here.
不要。
Don't.
我们有证据。
我们的采样是Zartan的。
We have proof.
We're taking it to Joe Cotton.
你照计划进行。
You planned this all along.
路霸，停下。
Block, stand down.
我们是不是律师。我们是军人。
We ain't lawyers. We're soldiers.
我告诉你，我要去
谁都会这样做的。
I told you I was gonna
find the man who did this.
我要杀了他。
I was gonna kill him.
没有！这是...别这么干！
No! That's... No. Negative!
路霸 路霸
Block. Block.
该死的！
Damn it!
一枪命中
One in the chamber.
路霸 路霸 你在哪儿
Block? Block, where are you?
我就是想看你这个表情
I want to see that face.
你终于知道今天就是你的死期
The one where you realise
today's the day.
你的表情就跟我那天在沙漠里
It's the face all those pretty little Joes
had in the desert
放烟火炸死你们的队员一样
when I lit them all up like fireworks!
我真想看你这个表情
I really want to see that face.
看到了吗
There it is.
如果眼镜蛇和Zartan
控制了白宫，
If Cobra and Zartan
are in the White House,
那这个世界就危险了
then the world is at stake.
风暴阴影。
Storm Shadow.
你可以告诉我们眼镜蛇的计划，
You will tell us Cobra's endgame,
或选择死亡
or die
你用来杀死刚大师的这把刀下
by the same sword you once
used to kill our master.
你的剑，
Your sword,
是我们爱戴的刚大师赐予你的
given to you
by our beloved Hard Master.
你是否承认是你的妒忌和仇恨
Do you deny that your envy and hatred
drove you to shed
使这上面沾上刚大师的血
the Hard Master's blood?
一段充满仇恨的人生
It's possible
to feel so much hate
已经感觉不到仇恨了
you stop feeling it at all.
像鱼一样的，不知道它是在水中。
Like a fish not knowing it's in water.
我的人生道路早已被选定
But my path was chosen for me
我的敌人
by my enemy
他把杀害大师的罪名套在我身上
who framed me
for killing the Hard Master.
而我的朋友们
And my friends
深信我是凶手
who believed it.
有眼无珠之辈 没有争辩的必要
Why defend yourself to men
too blind to see?
这是刚大师的血。
That is the Hard Master's blood.
但是，这是不是......
But that is not...
等一下！
Wait!
我的刀。
...my sword.
岚影族的刀是不会断的
Arashikage steel does not break.
我问自己一遍又一遍
I have asked myself over and over
是谁恨我恨到要毁了我的人生才行
who despised me enough
to destroy my life?
对不起，
风暴阴影。
I am sorry,
Storm Shadow.
可是什么人最能从你的痛苦中获利呢
But who would stand to gain the most
by framing you for this crime?
是你的童年时代给你蒙上了阴影
Your young adversary
who chased you away?
还是你后来跟随的人给你留下了阴影
Or the man into whose arms
you were chased.
有人收留了你
Someone who welcomed you,
对你展现出善意
showed you kindness.
他需要我。
He needed me.
我会成为谁。
For who I would become.
成了武艺精湛残酷的武士
A warrior of great skill and anger.
那个背叛我的人既能干又精明狡诈
The man who betrayed me
was capable of great ingenuity,
残忍
violence,
最可怕的是
but most of all,
伪装。
disguise.
Zartan。
Zartan.
是。
Yes.
请告诉我们，他和眼镜蛇有什么阴谋
Tell us what he and Cobra have planned
让我们一起对抗共同的敌人
so we can destroy our common enemy
一起来吧
together.
尽量保持静止。
Try to hold still.
你想要我怎么配合
应该再来一次袭击？
You want to remind me how knuckles
are supposed to strike again?
一起吗？
Together.
这些都是你的话。
Those were your words.
- 我有一个机会，我也做了。
- 现在，别说了！
- I had a shot and I took it.
- Now, don't give me that!
去你的。
You went rogue.
我会再次这样做。
And I'd do it again.
是吗？到底是什么东西
你的大计划，然后，对吧？
Yeah? And what was
your big plan, then, huh?
你希望你自己被打死？
You get yourself killed?
耶稣基督。我听到的一切
你说一遍又一遍。
Jesus Christ. I listened to everything
you said over and over again.
我从来没有质疑...
I never questioned...
我想牺牲更多的特种兵。
I wasn't going to bury any more Joes.
我要清理枪支。
I've got guns to clean.
嘿。
Hey.
来帮忙？
Help me out here?
谢谢。
Thanks.
如果我爸爸能看到我现在...
If my dad could see me now...
你说的是什么？
What are you talking about?
你不会相信的。
He wouldn't believe it.
为什么呢？
Why?
我们家三代都是军人
Third generation military.
爸爸想培养第四代
Desperately wanted a fourth, and
我妈却生了我。
my mom had me.
那么，他一定是
真正为你感到骄傲吧
Well, he must be
real proud of you, then.
他不相信
在女战士。
He didn't believe
in female soldiers.
最后我问他为什么。他说，
I finally asked him why. He said
他不会把性命交到女人的手上
he didn't want to put his life
in the hands of a woman.
第二天我就入伍了
I enlisted the next day.
接下来的七年里
Spent the next seven years
我试图超越他
让他向我敬礼。
trying to outrank him
so he'd have to salute me.
你做到了吗
Did it work?
可惜他没看到就死了
He died before I got the chance.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
实际上，我喜欢穿红的。
I'm actually gonna miss the red.
挺好看的
You look real nice.
嘿。我说，我们有枪要清洁。
Hey. I said we got guns to clean.
世界不是本身保存。
The world ain't saving itself.
这一拳是为你征税打的
That was for the tax hike.
就好像你交过税似的
Like you pay taxes.
是不是总是我。
Ain't always about me.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
我们仍然需要这个人。
We still need the man.
他还有利用价值
Besides, we've grown close.
风暴阴影？
Is Storm Shadow in?
用不着你来操心 他的状态好得很
Don't you worry about him.
He'll be more than ready.
我实在不太看好你的内阁
I'm not too impressed with your Cabinet.
不就是经过听证会嘛 你就认了吧
No confirmation
hearings, that's what you get.
够了！
Enough!
接下来我说了算
I'll take it from here.
谁控制公文包，
He who controls this briefcase,
就控制美国的核武库
controls the U.S. nuclear arsenal
和人类的命运。
and the fate of humanity.
睁开你的眼睛，前总统先生。
Open your eyes, Mr Ex-President.
眼睛是心灵的窗户
The eyes are
the windows to the soul.
睁开
Open up.
宙斯是准备好了。
Zeus is ready.
我们只需要
最后一块拼图。
We just need
one final piece of the puzzle.
干得好。
Well done.
历史自会做出评判的
History will stand in judgment.
不是我。你。
Not of me. Of you.
怎么样了，JAYE？
What do we got, Jaye?
Zartan把重心都铺在这场核峰会上了
Zartan's entire focus
has been this nuclear summit.
这一定是他们计划的核心
It has to be the key
to whatever he's planning.
好的。好吧，那么这就是我们的目标。
All right. Well, then that's our target.
嗯。
Yeah.
伙计们，走。
Guys, move.
我觉得我速度比你快 蛇眼
I think I'm faster than you, Snake Eyes.
该死的忍者。
Damn Ninjas.
很高兴见到你，兄弟。
Good to see you, brother.
JAYE。
Jaye.
金克斯。
Jinx.
都退后
Back up.
他是自己人
He's with us.
我不是自己人
I am not with you.
但是，这一次，
But for this once,
我不和你们作对
I am not against you.
他杀死我们的人有多少？
How many of our men has he killed?
和他并肩作战吧
We're supposed to fight with him?
大国首领们明天要汇聚一堂 这是一个陷阱。
The leaders of the world
will gather tomorrow. It's a trap.
风暴是唯一一个
知道眼镜蛇计划的人
Storm is the only one
who knows Cobra's plan
他可以帮助我们阻止计划。
inside and out.
He can help us find a way to stop it.
大家得精诚合作
But we have to work together.
好的。
All right.
行动。
Let's move.
圣诞快乐。
Merry Christmas.
哇塞，还有你这样的邻居呀！
Makes you wonder
about your neighbours.
漂亮
Nice.
打开的沙发上。
Open up that couch.
什么？
Anything?
我自己带。
I brought my own.
很好
Nice.
就是它了
Yeah, that'll work.
嘿。
Hey.
这可是我的珍藏
That one's mine.
这真的是巴顿将军的枪，是不是？
This really is Patton's gun, isn't it?
他们家族送我的。
Gift from his family.
至高的荣耀
What an honour.
的确是
You bet.
我倒是觉得你该找个与你块头相称的
I was actually thinking about
something a little more your size.
尽量别刮伤了
Try not to scratch her up.
挂空档时不太稳定
Idles a little rough in neutral.
我才不会挂空档呢
I ain't gonna be in neutral.
呼啊。
Hoo-ah.
你怎么样？
What about you?
国防部说
我不能出山。
DOD says
I can't come out of retirement.
可没规定我不能重新入伍
They didn't say anything
about reenlisting.
报告，军士长。
Reporting for duty, Sergeant Major.
还有几个朋友要加入进来
I'd like to bring a couple friends of mine.
科尔顿的球队，
很荣幸和你们合作
Colton's team,
it's our honour.
你们先负责外围
You guys take the perimeter.
弗林特，JAYE，蛇眼，
你们从侧翼夹击。
Flint, Jaye, Snake,
you guys take the flank.
金克斯和风暴，里外配合。
Jinx and Storm, Trojan Horse.
Zartan会拿着公文包。
Zartan will be holding the briefcase.
风暴将是他最亲密的人。
Storm will be the closest man to him.
但要等全员就位才能行动
But he can't move
until we're all in position.
所有人要盯紧目标
Everyone keep your eye on the prize.
保住了核心 就保住了全局
We secure the football,
we secure the world.
蛇眼，你觉得呢
Snake, how's all that sound?
这就是我想的。
That's what I thought.
好吧，等一下。
Okay, wait. Hold on a second.
敌人布置装甲部队的方位
在这里，这里，和这里。
We still have enemy armour
here, here, and here.
对吗？
Right?
装甲车一过来 我们就完了
These tanks survive, we don't.
装甲车由我来对付
Leave the tanks to me.
将军？
General?
叫我特种兵
Call me Joe.
- 我错过了什么？
- 没有
- Anything I missed?
- No.
滴水不漏 我的任务呢
Rock solid. My orders?
总统。营救总统
The President.
- 布伦达跟我一组。
- 收到。
- Brenda's with my team.
- Roger that.
布兰达有选择权吗
Does Brenda get a vote?
没有。
Negative.
你需要一支钢笔吗？
You need a pen?
我需要你的帮助。
I need your help.
好的。
All right.
让我们大干一场！呼啊！
Let's kick that ass! Hoo-ah!
呼啊！
Hoo-ah!
一个历史性的日子
A historic day for
美国总统
他会见...
the President of the United States
as he meets with...
今天下午，
总统将会见
This afternoon, the
President is meeting with the leaders
8个核大国的领导人。
of the eight nuclear powers.
以前从未
有一个总统如此大胆
Never before
has a President been so bold
召集世界的领袖...
to call the leaders
of the world together...
这将是
前所未有的核谈判
These are
unprecedented nuclear talks
大部分人感觉是出乎意料
that most believed would never happen.
会议安全的问题一定是最高机密
You can bet security is
at its highest...
我们将进一步迈向前所未有的无核世界
We may be closer
to a nuclear-free world
比我们曾经去过。
than we have ever been.
世界领导人们，
My fellow world leaders,
欢迎来到
萨姆特堡，
welcome to the hallowed grounds
of Fort Sumter,
这些围墙见证我们国家的严重的内战的第一炮
whose proud walls saw the first shots
in our nation's grievous Civil War.
在这里，官兵疯狂地违背了原则
Here, men rushed through the breach
in a madness.
好好反省错误吧
What better place to step back
from that same breach.
放弃我们的阴暗的本性。
Renounce our darker natures.
原谅我们的敌人。
Forgive our staunchest foes.
这是个有象征意义的地方
This site is symbolic.
我们寻求实现的和平
Not only for the peace
we seek to achieve,
避免战火
but the conflagration we seek to avoid.
今天眼镜蛇保护我们
The Cobras who protect us today
他们有着比和平
are dedicated to the belief
that there is no greater peace
更平和的心态。
than peace of mind.
- 谢谢你。
- Thank you.
我再说一遍。
I'll say it again.
世界因为有核武器才会变得更安全
The world is safer
with a nuclear presence.
我敢肯定，你的选民会很喜欢
我们的最终建议。
I'm sure your electorate will be happy
by our final proposal.
到2016年减少50％。
50% reduction by 2016.
在场有很多国家的领袖
There are a lot of leaders in this room.
但是，只有一个自由世界的领导者。
But only one leader of the free world.
而他，
And he,
就是我 请听我说
I, stay with me,
我要求在场各位都能实现全面销毁核武器
asked you here with the goal
of universal disarmament.
创造无核世界
Nuclear zero.
我已经把好话都讲完了
Now, I was prepared
to cajole to get what I want.
现在我下硬指令
I'm now at threaten.
你们都要给我立即销毁库存核武器
Each of you will clear out
his nuclear closet immediately.
假如没有做到的话 就会被认为是宣战的举动
Failure to participate
will be considered an act of war.
你是在开玩笑，当然。
You're joking, of course.
本次峰会结束。
This summit is over.
那么这是什么。
Then this is it.
可是先生们
This is it, boys.
这个国家向你们宣战
This country is at war.
你和你和你
你，你，你。
With you and you and you
and you and you and you.
1组就位 1组开始行动
Delta team in position.
Echo, you're a go.
这里是1组 展开攻击
This is Echo. Beginning assault.
美国核武库
The U.S. nuclear arsenal
足以把你们每个国家毁灭14次
is capable of destroying
each of your countries 14 times over.
确切地说能毁灭北韩15次
Fifteen, in the case of North Korea,
just to be sure.
这一切
And all
只需要按下
at the push
一个按钮。
of a button.
这可是真的呀！
It's true. Yeah!
是啊，我按。
Yeah, I pressed it.
你已经失去了你的心！
You have lost your mind!
这是相对的。
It's all relative.
你有三分钟时间来决定。
You got three minutes to decide.
- 戴上手表了吗？
- 保持无线电静默。
- You got next watch?
- Maintain radio silence.
我们不会同意 也不能再坐视不管了
We cannot, we will not leave
a legacy of acquiescence!
- 把公文包拿来。
- Bring the briefcase.
不要这样做！
Don't do this!
可有没有赢家！
There can be no winners!
哦。高得分。
Ooh. High score.
让历史来见证吧 看由谁为这疯狂承担责任
Let history record
who was responsible for this madness.
发射。
Launch.
看好翡翠城。
Eyes on the Emerald City.
JAYE、科尔顿
你们去找总统。
Jaye and Colton,
you're a go for POTUS.
你没事吧？
You all right?
嗯。你没事吧？
Yeah. You all right?
我的胆固醇有点高。
My cholesterol's a little high.
Jaye和科尔顿。
岗哨搞定。
Jaye and General Colton.
Checkpoint neutralised.
这儿交给你了
You're on your own.
哦 好消息是下个月不用再开全球气候变暖峰会了
Well, the good news is,
no global warming summit next month.
除非
Unless
我们当中有人在乎他在历史上留下的地位
one of us cared enough
about his place in history
单方面关闭了他的弹头。
to unilaterally disable his warheads.
嗯？
Hmm?
为了子孙后代
You know, in the name of the children.
有谁自愿
Any volunteers?
没有 那好。
No? Fine.
我。
Me.
打电话给你的人确认。
Call your people to confirm.
你是不是真的疯了
You're a complete lunatic.
眼看就要摧毁亚洲。
Says the man about to destroy Asia.
来吧，
没人跟风？
Come on,
who's going to follow suit, huh?
你们真要打算眼睁睁地看着地球被毁灭掉吗
Are you really going to stand by
and watch as Earth is destroyed?
中止！
Abort!
我猜最后一个会是北韩
I figured North Korea for last.
我爱的小家伙。
Got to love the little guy.
先生们
Gentlemen.
欢迎来到一个无核武器的世界。
Welcome to a nuclear-free world.
我想请大家把注意力转移到自己祖国的实况画面上
I want to direct your attention
to live images of your homelands.
现在，你们正在看到
一个先进的武器系统
Now, you're looking
at an advanced weapons system
我们称之为宙斯计划。
we call Project Zeus.
有七个宙斯卫星
绕地球轨道。
There are seven Zeus satellites
orbiting Earth.
每颗卫星都带有
10个空心铂管
Each satellite contains
10 hollow platinum tubes
填充用钨棒。
filled with a tungsten rod.
宙斯卫星 目标A 锁定伦敦
Zeus satellite 1-A approaching London.
坐标已经输入 进入投放程序
Ordnance live and loaded.
Awaiting drop authorisation.
为了让钨棒击中目标 我们根本无需发射
Now, to direct a rod to its target,
we don't launch it or fire it.
扔下去就是了
We drop it!
剩下的事地心引力办
Gravity does the rest.
好好看吧
Observe.
1-A卫星。
我们远程发射授权。
Satellite 1-A.
We have remote launch authorisation.
三，二，一，
Three, two, one,
投放。
drop.
钨棒落下的速度比子弹要快八倍
A rod touches down
eight times faster than a bullet.
而它的杀伤力则比核弹头要大得多了
And with a force significantly greater
than a nuclear warhead.
不会产生辐射尘。
None of the fallout.
但会带来乐趣
All of the fun.
你必须对此负责
You will have to
answer for this.
你的国会 你的最高法院 会放过你吗
To your Congress, your courts.
错了 是他们要对我负责
Correction,
they will have to answer to me.
你想要的是什么呢？
What is it you want?
我想得到全部
I want it all.
眼镜蛇革命已经开始。
The Cobra revolution has begun.
只要我按下这个按钮
Zartan就会启动自动投射程序。
By pressing that button,
Zartan initiated an auto-drop sequence.
我宙斯卫星的
正在进入位置
My Zeus satellites
are moving into position
向剩余的六个国家飞去
over your six remaining countries.
卫星通过7-A 2-A
途中目标。
Satellites 2-A through 7-A
en route to targets.
同一个按钮可以启动 也可以终止
The same button that begins this
can end it.
但对于交易我有个先决条件
But I only press it for a price.
把整个政权交给我
Total allegiance.
路霸 解决外围的敌人
Block, secure the perimeter!
没什么比手提箱更重要 别让特种部队拿到
Get the control case from Zartan.
I'm going to drop them all.
去门那儿！走，走，走！
Head to the door! Go, go, go!
卫星正向目标前进。
Satellites en route to targets.
开始执行指令程序
Beginning command protocols.
跟着队伍！去！
Follow that ground team! Go!
留下来。
Stay.
六点方向，两个眼镜蛇！
On your six, Cobra two!
眼镜蛇，眼镜蛇之一，
我需要眼睛！眼睛！
Cobra one, Cobra one,
I need eyes on! Eyes on!
该死的。
Damn it.
我们已经得到了她走投无路。
We've got her cornered.
她是不会去任何地方。
She ain't going anywhere.
去！
Go!
风暴。
我从来没有想过你会是特种队员。
Storm.
I never figured you for a Joe.
我对你很失望。
I'm very disappointed in you.
你是欠扁的。
You're a bitch to hit.
叛徒。
Traitor.
风暴。
Storm.
你知道，这把宝剑
从来没有打算
You know, this sword
was never intended
对任何人愤怒。
for anyone
with anger management issues.
轰！
Boom!
- 那是什么？
- 闭嘴。
- What was that?
- Shut up.
雷 - ？
- 是的，先生。
- Ray?
- Yes, sir.
检查门。汇报情况。
Check the door. Give me a sit rep.
我就可以了。
I'm on it.
你们两个守住入口。
You two secure the entrance.
- 你在做什么？
- 让我们去。我们离开这里。
- What are you doing?
- Let's go. We're out of here.
站了下来。我要毙了他！
Stand down. I'm gonna shoot him!
我说退下！
I said stand down!
既然是特种部队的 就把枪放下 让我们出去
Be a good G.I. Joe and drop the gun.
We're walking out of here.
我会打爆他的头
你明白我的意思吗？
I will shoot him in the head.
Do you understand me?
你不听，是吗？
把枪放下！
You're not listening, are you?
Put the gun down!
把枪放下
Drop it!
放松 放松
Easy, easy.
压住伤口
Put some pressure on it.
将军科尔顿。
General Colton.
这是很高兴见到你。
- 很高兴见到你。
-It's good to see you.
- Good to see you.
- 对不起 总统先生 - 没关系
- Sorry, Mr President.
- No, it's fine.
来吧。让我们继续前进。
Come on. Let's move.
在这里，我们走了。
Here we go.
路霸 第一任务完成 没有伤亡。
Roadblock, POTUS secure.
No casualties.
收到 珍
Roger that, Jaye.
是你背叛了刚大师
You betrayed the Hard Master.
搞得我就是我。
And made me what I am.
没错。
Yep.
是的，我可以看到那是错误的。
Yeah, I can see that was wrong.
我们继续找到萤火虫和眼镜蛇
ROADBLOCK. We need eyes
on Firefly and Cobra ASAP.
院子里安全 没有看到他们
Courtyard clear. No sign of him.
指挥官，我有这种情况。
Commander, I have the case.
我们仍然是一个去。
We are still a go.
直到滴多久？
How long till drop?
在时间表上，指挥官。
五分钟的实弹射击。
On schedule, Commander.
Five minutes to live fire.
最终的目标即将开始。
Final targeting to begin shortly.
宙斯卫星4和图7中的位置。
Zeus satellites 4 and 7 in position.
：宙斯卫星2，3，5，和6个
被锁定的目标。法国，
Zeus satellites 2, 3, 5, and 6
are locked on target. France,
俄罗斯，朝鲜，
Russia, North Korea,
印度，以色列，中国。
India, Israel, China.
路霸
Block.
眼镜蛇跑了
Cobra Commander's bugging out.
没有萤火虫的迹象。
No sign of Firefly.
我对付他
I've got him.
目标已锁定 武器装填完毕
Targets acquired.
Ordnance live and loading.
宙斯4号准备发射 程序开启
Zeus 4 is ready to fire. Hatch is open.
- 干掉他 快 - 干掉他
- Get him!
- Take him out!
你想这种情况下？
You want that case?
你得先放倒我
You're gonna have to come through me.
哦，是的。
Oh, yeah.
这是正确的。
That's right.
所有卫星已经开始负载
最后的倒计时。
All satellites have begun load
for final countdown.
启动代码确认。
Launch codes confirmed.
十秒钟住火。
Ten seconds to live fire.
十位。
Ten.
九。
Nine.
八。
Eight.
七。六。
Seven. Six.
五。
Five.
四。
Four.
三。
Three.
二。
Two.
威胁终止。
Threat terminated.
呼叫B组外围已经清理完毕
Team Bravo, perimeter has been
cleared and secured.
特种部队已经接管了眼镜蛇指挥中心
Joe Command to
covert operations.
并且控制了周边局势
We have control of the perimeter.
医务人员在现场。
Medical personnel are on the scene.
特种部队成员 没有伤亡
All Joes are accounted for.
我们要回家了。
We're going home.
总统是
平安回来今天在白宫椭圆形办公室，
The President is
back safe in the Oval Office today,
为特种部队主持受奖仪式
presiding over a ceremony
honouring the G.I. Joes.
随着世界恢复秩序，
With the world
back in order,
世界各地已经开始重建。
rebuilding has begun around the world.
那些
谁站在我们旁边，
Those
who stand beside us,
世人只知道他们是特种部队
the world knows them as Joes.
我们知道他们是英雄。
We know them as heroes.
金克斯。
Jinx.
欢迎加入特种部队
Welcome to the Joes.
弗林特。
Flint.
干得漂亮
Great job.
队长JAYE伯内特。
Captain Jaye Burnett.
我和你父亲是战友
I served with your father.
他会很为你感到骄傲。
He'd be very proud of you.
女士们 先生们 向特种部队致敬
Ladies and gentlemen, the G. I. Joes.
嘿。
Hey.
等你找到眼镜蛇的时候用
For when you find Cobra Commander.
我们在哪里可以找到你，将军？
Where can we find you, General?
等我进一步的命令
Just need my orders.
你知道，我们的团队将所向无敌。
You know, we'd make a hell of a team.
@经典电影的那点事  www.TBmovie.com